[{"topicId":"8","id":"8000","langCode":"en","question":"qkmdlejPLtklS+14r10dzlJ+4DS61XYieiCFjVqB85q73N6of5lkLUSqERtqbfC0","answers":["take care of","give up","account for","take over"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"FN1dEKIrFk9JHOB9Ce6BlVb/iVPCT+wddtYoGZhH9ALJmrjXDHda6zIGbWRMf9RgslB6R/Da+H/wgsbHcc2D1TXxNwhznlvu4E2avruNjWrO78KG9Mk9XD2pwUKhkyZmV7wjwPYIeHOxqYFpHdV6IOw5G8aRZD5yRzpgJU3OQhwXdvS0LMrzL9ig7y9hWvOdywZ6+cjEscrI6I5Sj08TrOGxR2CWOB+QsiKjj/JgvrJn9Hnoki+GaosowPjvnD04I8MKl6w8M/li0ZlCun5LLEnnUn7Ss73vVTIk53kdaMnfwrDmCuw7roBeLltbFX4BHGEzzFcKJTGwmsE3i4AS61qHgUOkhTBVEVSTvmjmK38AQI3nelnTgO9ioRG7P+uF+uZV0C1jpRxLM9cuOppgfhI2pdOXXaqezRas2s4OE4xcp2GyeYhA5c5vabuTUJrAq6uHAmvgfF9xG3RgYmh0i5u53EJwQEdd62pO0Q4S+Bw\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8001","langCode":"en","question":"Sx4Lt4mzV/uh6sD2La1cnwc6wd5njSqtEQfUs35EgBc\u003d","answers":["brings up","blows up","calls for","blows out"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"vJLXYmqIr3V5JRwlNdcaIRJDBqJCe1NfE9Lqa7aGVCMysivolUL0C3rAgym99xshSEjmmx3wFzw9axQMeZzs3oOh4rtihS1ExECzCyI3F8rH1SoOj9nvXt+uLOlkQpUbfMvACSNYAnsDyZ42cA9DfEaujvzorz0yeWUy1zoQT+ap/U44J3Q4lsP0Cacia3qo8WqZC1hU0RWK91ByfsgNfqbSYfYZTp+1RDL8il1rMDcl1PSKuqT5TV1TLK9D1PlD2RWJOnTtUg1M/kGx2YawG8/W70X+BLvaF/bKy0/f8rdLyH18U+QUY4nMnzsvfBErYhKnBKWncl2/uPlgqNh0c83HbnkwhobmXdVkKVcLCSSEbzIZIy8f/vBQNmIt/pHh"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8002","langCode":"en","question":"yFfZvBfJApwks4lPE2VxlqfGI9YVelW45jjS48AMlzLKj79ziDZgSgpHsmlCLfZZ10KsF+yGrKksrXwn1GsXuQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["call off","call on","look for","come up"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"VRCNvEwkFFvu0VgJDOXEUQGjTf7OPUoDvbD9kc3c9GE1Phve8xf7rVlYjoTvagkYzZv+eLE4t9q69oWIxBFhD46W90FIiAaCdMD0QxpMmhZN4uW73pg1DHtr1WpmwkRGdUGUeT0G7/O1uzyGm4o/n1wrDiH1IBJLRjH7ujnpyWJkGNjB4bnA2Nq9gQkGQojEmtVfRD8v73ximuzUBunDsc5iB6RpCnA8hK4+sFK2dVzqgzyreUG+q+Hul7bncmVaJaOmg5MgBVcMaG3ZJfd3TA\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8003","langCode":"en","question":"OAXMkTjZR+gSEmHxq3WZ1PHF5mhUgAKjVTOiJqNgIU6mQBxSdJsJkFW3xY+VfOES","answers":["bring in","handed in","brought up","hold up"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"4tZz0cMUjlzrwuAZSmYwe55bhxFmTIyn4yP5TGG7NrXSUwPjPApmuKjDKkBFRRQNg4+sqbCGrUZEQe/eExmzLnxv4KM3Ho7dbnxEc3a2H7oy3laZm56ic0YEilIp1G6lGCUfJRtFvWeLnrO6t2yLFrpDds0domCVCVXx0d3Qf6Voc/5Lo3uKPKC6LO8cIf1PryG0h5vqUDFxUC5sTy31qvyCHdfodSm/S76pYliXQuwa2knS60TYlK1R4E9WIdqucKL7iXR+eI/0HW9i5nT0xlfzG3n0ArUgfnknBFwKYyniyJhlsLKC67hiktfzMCDF"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8004","langCode":"en","question":"T4XYSIbWYS6kl1hRmUDypzLue/5zx4vqEl8VjEZ4/Xs\u003d","answers":["hold on","grow up","go on","give out"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"CkGX5V8daHMy2Kw1RPl51OoBWdYg0MOArwMXZVPezsse1uMMj5Nf4DdL+U9nPlpO+jnjcdEx3IORjsNgQ/VgN8O1Jl6fk6XvAvMyBVgqcgHYf8RA2t7kKzmNR2duJLefSw53d8XxhBAQezRpj1gVAdA7bT+Jjd3tk196XmeutCnc7vD6OJPKPptNOD5Lf1yw5NMlVyYv3G1IoCXe0+P3M3SbUXfoKUWA+zGwAOExO3uTpTpobeDarbPznjTzM4XvKgY7b888u4ISWT3y4TDpL5iL6LumcNM2NJUi4G4yIjIkUi4rqDdJAo2yHVNcUARH"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8005","langCode":"en","question":"xkbBTq7kf0ijFq323eOsYCRX6wiJ3oq0ujmbL5i/3fZd8/MfO+tPjggtbrxDnUfAZDeXjigcwhrbk403JFp7DA\u003d\u003d","answers":["got over","got up ","gave up","got on "],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"J8Q/XBliSxyvEe6OFO6y4SeMo4pzMwyG4yM2UJPfG2FrhJgLZ4p8oPpmynRRvV9o2nW3aXVx5MyJ0/7t1/i/v9hEiWc5suvn4z3OB3N6XStL9/0lb+x14pcCNfJyi5TxGzCpJa8dymE1h0m7te2i9Y2E+8FS5HjYdGX3tTzQ4keBreefSTC8Jb+AMBywNznw8EjSvDnF6TowKDRP4tKkvzUANyr74z+bUWn3oxreRzUiVBJ2/fNYd++hXOsEdkq8t0ZlSQr7HVHoFg3pLqghA19yorFLhadns5r+GP5dVNSYi+i7pnDTNjSVIuBuMiIyJFIuK6g3SQKNsh1TXFAERw\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8006","langCode":"en","question":"HryMv0/YFyRdS02K6ILfJWGYwfl8Ka7/xclLJoiT6sfV8KOUxPEi7Y7nIt6OGE4RnoJ4sE4szWtJ8G/46S0muqfy32oA69xhNyPGmDofVwVS5myLsCtyRklufvs/4YnQ","answers":["stands out","sets up","takes on","puts on"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"lGTOd4oT7zy+w/KCZ5W9yxJb6zJ785cTYppgBytdk/sEuECbTlBRxD5crzetJFqUnW08aB+KEaNkHvNlD/bJY11RwfTianEpYDX42Qyocqc9oHqIpbK9y7o7/k65MOKKqy14jdr73VlWPhZ9qKM1vuGxR2CWOB+QsiKjj/JgvrKwlK+CdkZ3uWylW15wgF0eARCTlWaEpGUDiAdE+ZKaZu1N1PjOVYnjqALZHOBd/xdiEqcEpadyXb+4+WCo2HRzzcdueTCGhuZd1WQpVwsJJIRvMhkjLx/+8FA2Yi3+keE\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8007","langCode":"en","question":"4oTO8xT8Wqj1Q6FWmFxHmnXAVVhAPaGkRYpy9BQQgo2WFe5i9gbq7Mm04zlw7r15TJjH2wr8mYihLtWy7245LA\u003d\u003d","answers":["take after","put up with","put forward","take care of"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"rUHFBmGO9Jslx6v23jM2ZGzugddwkVLDmwPRxTDbBLxJM9klaiYhHNxMs2Q0lDLns03BypUsdpeLhKXH4JgwU8RTUqxKWS7MEeDgjkYO1yIBWy/36IeAyVbBT9H7vYSwrSEb84liEOAQejaVSeWh2wVzKihVjVSpbDXrwyMobFbA0F+qxIX2W45siWcUodPLslB6R/Da+H/wgsbHcc2D1TXxNwhznlvu4E2avruNjWrO78KG9Mk9XD2pwUKhkyZmV7wjwPYIeHOxqYFpHdV6IOw5G8aRZD5yRzpgJU3OQhwXdvS0LMrzL9ig7y9hWvOdxdWn4fmZXDj/niVQziDYzYdwLnNxeCyHwbmwZint76qjeVkFocO/LPXaLYzLqyI4eGZIDTbvCDhBpw6+eqfE+R0UDNW8CWTpfGbsI729OkyR0d5AzTX5/XUdyxNHEkn+ODdvBUeviTCXer/qOIsK8Y9O2Kf3/C4iKtDIrt8u7a1rv6rUDyyBknbPMVxdbtwPQfN8/CEcV0FeLrR2uk6ukw\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8008","langCode":"en","question":"mcA66ru5tf/+aH/hiZgZ24p9YTKFJLmxahNScqIo3du/mGPQWML1MkRsWmEbRr00","answers":["gets off","takes on","takes off","talks over"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"oQ1oP183q6U+6t6oCz57IiWI9DN3ElPmGd9TL30F9TZeBgzC0hf/UE7x05dHtdeZbUGIsNHwlurZ4rhCzNsT7BaZD7ZmryULjuG3ObY4g9tyNGmw6s+/sgAPNbcpRA6eA6QAEW1mRaSc5Y3GcZyKdpBMxixXn18uezAbh/U7svkGiLWzRAWhWW60yn1GyqWB4bFHYJY4H5CyIqOP8mC+srCUr4J2Rne5bKVbXnCAXR63yjGEQIM/eC1rPmpLsOPiIwncmKVfEK0YhCnQEX94BwEQk5VmhKRlA4gHRPmSmma7nZmEmknLPRdtD1gIICT3YhKnBKWncl2/uPlgqNh0c83HbnkwhobmXdVkKVcLCSSEbzIZIy8f/vBQNmIt/pHh"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8009","langCode":"en","question":"I3sW7wjtbWPv1oN/zOx1s2vcdD5fDrWIOy1iBoKN26Fjlxq3vykh25owdm5lZznqQ0tAoSR83Wx+9o2FItD/YjaUvZVpL2HKOq+k79XLgE2EbzIZIy8f/vBQNmIt/pHh","answers":["running out ","setting off ","taking over ","showing up "],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"hPJ1nR24vTnADV2E3woWUohB7zlZtTkP1A0oNpjudC5eUPwuMK7DOoYcRTRFjTyq8qOc6nkDS5jCH+CV8zeRjCIU2+KcXvQZ0FKJyazeFTvonIJK++oIqbmaf+dP7K7eMWlRuzSVZbqNrGtdfztYoetVHwEIuW6N6BKmkFi4BhPb36vjO+ZN0rzKM2c3e4DX1jFnszUizcpBNBif+pwiljFFQEUWpCFYtiAsY9SEIp9k6rT8skGU0R81DsLPav6qcyUTx3d9vUtJv+p7WD9zlRaY49mgNtYg/JJnWK/q5ACg9XgvF90vZc0G4ARUM6+DOFopz9PLQcHfpWY7L7pyFnJj9r1Q7aq/Lc1mZ7kHj07sgLzBscQOyVImsWMZh3R7NFhIq7VBanp1mkCoTy/KyLgcDMcr4TATVSiBEwqTWCovKrts7+bHr0jjotwWCzCh"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8010","langCode":"en","question":"JhVsdobIRHIRrYJFbQdJGNfI1awiTUJhC+OjEM9DCcc1oaA7wKHuZqSja8qn12wv","answers":["fix up ","shut up ","set up","grow up "],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"xY0DSyxMMKE2CT6wu3V+WEyC3NL5q96ehQ3tmiudyV6OwZrs2kW67LjHEjmjpykykRUptqM4WO/RTXpbYj+BLpc1CxMnCxqBUTpWiHtV/oWhJb6Zl1ruLzvL0qYalSHisHdM8zokHC+HBSkNi6NIUW3wRBF4rCM6vrpBGl7TSATbcEaNhwniyQEYW1+ZWmdMkCpoSNX1Cnm52K+zY/peonTbarC0XUn15afqntIgq7O9HzJ0rafoiidIKtfP1Er/0TnWfyKD3qtL1/xRFozm6Q\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8011","langCode":"en","question":"KOGccIfzilHCFK0a8V5aDzYTJ4coCbA+bC6PBViObf2Xzf0G3semlJMCi2Es4kS8gPKR87TdsUeUcb63rj649g\u003d\u003d","answers":["go over","get by","show off","cut down"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"xv6tDDbydfiuZSIMQIqd3VC2ucguzI4nCzLfsews+4ioA+3K2ec4V9P7eV8PEtwKTGRjRJoJ5t/R3I3E6CpeRxGR1CVmh9JmwP8fj0O5jSMNkksn6HDd/PGiHPWtiSp1dDbO4Z3USijeMWxmSDXbsfTjJCuQ+tFnHiIasweNfmW2HXSwXWAErJ0dpluf0C5v7jKUSyOrWILcU3jA4I/iQMJ/KS44F/FpmHp24ogKl4HOR/bpe3NHvq1BvJm5BRSZBlpl0N7M4F8Mek1a7zpBASENj2v/p8XgQk+NFshulO+puPgdhewWFdzBxwbkZQ5n"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8012","langCode":"en","question":"8RJs8NwxSsDbZ3E8FYVXV+Xgn+HSQLCYztPFUJtV9xc4/zguPGIvOHDSLJWNqJ4Vp2HhoaXQHRH2retcHVsJVVbbmhqxSn6m1I9WGK0xSn4\u003d","answers":["keep up with","break into","get on well with","come up to"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"NLlIZgXIy9AGj3evZc1F2yFd0YZXnRnCsgd3EyhcKCX8y18DHe1KD49jGImpfEa6b2swXIsq7FaeJrWRMmEBvb2L6AqmHbO8QW75DeI1Ts3Vh6royRfxLBlTQ4dCHUrCFbzlazMeZNGeNPDQ/uHjAwpFgKE21aqZhJh1+qfj0y2QLBddETTJ+4sxUqbKsl7+ss06GUZk1uhgxX5jIuLM8KQoh/5aLLS9cKcmy47ziCVZTOvXvSrk1y5LJZnvbpCyzXkfVGrtOaYbdw3Yyoxqsb3wR3iDU5DQxzAg9UugKd5hM1VGryYPgKuam5Z5B3CAvywEQk8rpZjYzalzJmluSAL6Y9o95alvRibUgx7kZEYDSsXYo0bNdC5AoQY5DiV5BI9qVw98+MLfxwUZioU0pdewalXLp834un/HhbGjVZ8hDY9r/6fF4EJPjRbIbpTvqbj4HYXsFhXcwccG5GUOZw\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8013","langCode":"en","question":"a7idz+/Wg01SxNSJD/+YEyLDOrqyo0fygNwdMqjrpduWhhZHR+zywNsMPsqI8n2ectg7aLmI9JiPjVh/XCeXKQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["look up to","look back on","look into","look for"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"kJLnaIbFJeLtBOuIl3bfWKYD/Ql/OZiuKnWkOXOSEdZXm3AGZS8+j8Y/qS1wn42a4GtJ6r46PFEjcPaeCnHXKAqIS9K0SzES/E6Nu+rihLZkVooXRmXDTAsdNgsByQmL2Gd2LLbgcJfRC3UemhYu6CRDf4hNLYFXlPL4ahUk6gi5rNlH8XxPMaMzFaSOePuPA0xXu7OE1NQEW896mwqnZmXqtJBCLUO0CD4pEnF4RXn3pDuTQbRGXSxWA3tqcPJoyIkxlAL9q3z4OwFmWIZfoMu5WjMqLreWfyGzb0qzxPprv6rUDyyBknbPMVxdbtwPNk1PUgvcMR7XR6OERyyU8g\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8014","langCode":"en","question":"bsK7Z3U9/ADuVD9g47CM8nKmViu4xlrjBHW3QMrr+KTmNiMO6us4rmUYsMgM5oCzRTDJVLBNw0m9Eag2YAGiGw\u003d\u003d","answers":["looking into","going away","giving out","going away"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"uBFs1frap2yFde9evmU/urbtcqgi7wlm+pLKPJmd9mfZnbEwZJRJsQwUPsnzhM7xtMDSa8hVRCv85bqgr8kEJyzvxTCJuHYiDIZ5RX3qsCssDUhH6p1peXiTKNewNwADlXNsfHy7c+r5lUEa936soZ35+vpEGb4Zs4HsX5H9xufvFhPYCx7no8DO88Ht+5E4mXdHBD0ABko4wYbmxD7Z5lLfmjb5fU4EEopj60ZiPsI4vm0Npu4765lOY3my0ZSex9VnSbUxbcRGZ/STH7nq5FLtVGVHSf4brdy31fx7Vb5Lf3pw0d1LB14EUuIwdDBZxw4AQsg3VZB/nj8mqF4atercWLtsPBN0BWXpoK731ao\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8015","langCode":"en","question":"r8pJ09aSeWo3S3HZ3n49doJcD8cqkoY9iA39gZZKPkwzl1PJMNEUSm0F655nBxNE","answers":["look out","bring up","call for","break down"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"GRvX1qeTbg89dfkvYZj4zuZHcxGW1mPSF3qnICC7SsjOEEQhG67+Pz0pMS//A2JHEE3HtwnSznaGkS9P3H+2rUjGehLx7n/qElvtVsH53C7jRqSk6BDaLP5x6c5CpVpM1jaEaqc9Ea91PWAL0/0RExwK5n8wff/peL7YeNoAkioIA+uVPzO+Yh7dZW1fSW042pgl4SnIqvTZ9k3mwOp6AFhexIQHznJjgrLGJ3+CxctnzXxP3xGjoDtpKOzpLLDe/aRCa2gDceClb8teqJ/wv7SCFJU/QfB8Tzm8wfyXs9RLf3pw0d1LB14EUuIwdDBZxw4AQsg3VZB/nj8mqF4ataOeRjIuj0ze0D4lZaA+lfs\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8016","langCode":"en","question":"0tHxZcEL1IIo2s27adzvG5Sh8TWuNs/lBVBSiHIuUjuTTa4zYXipnwxxZdDcwqLIURVp6+IzvzpGeOwhNdycwJLVJP9O8dnBGHgKyE3v8Mc\u003d","answers":["turned down","came about","turned into","bear out"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"KE+ZJU1KuYS8rqK/CFM0pYItzAjjUIDdpnA9cKAvo6EDLEF2BL6k2hWn002U9Wyr6Kl0mVBkZVhW4DS7igtg+W2G+easjluvAhvPXaZ3ZUjQEIIEBCFqDisP6wgCy2xs1TyISOVFVnMS+P0RdlVPnW7fO9e63OP75rnEb8Zbvn86UaKA+nQDC8EG17ii+lKXOhJJcxKGDeHVN7dfP3SJ2nbfotcuLVdJJPlu3LIOsQNXDNaoD3x8i/MhCKUUoKYZCIzTvkTHsp/4BOPa4jMlZhQ5MBLR73+q6PmM9QFNJscPyJjxRJvDog01GiKL3s8ScFWzodZs4r2p3jLLsbipVojczPpyf1p67Hleg/gU87X1TyWwxKx5WgqMrDE8LEicYlC69JryxgpYcwXneavfDNwKqCpGSZB6f8DdqS6gXa61VQ4N2KPa6Oq54EplOl8Z"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8017","langCode":"en","question":"TF2lXxlj+Emuf8Nb5zJTe7cunbAQB5h60TXNu/LdnbEEemT1oUh68MQ3fkQefmrbP2mF6zL430PIp5xqTbOfGw\u003d\u003d","answers":["catch up with","go in for","clear up","carry out"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"RNK+SiqUp0BgRb6yGoabaqvMUDLm8EGIX1MR/FxTSUeX9ZoiQebIP9AjMWtbTQcdsNZXHD3QrsJCbvgyoAFwAAadueA/rxCs6BC5++2LTOvrALyARtYH7eE6aoTuRuUG2ebU1GlgzjRGqRuJex3+xak8Ptnu2NMdxnRldIwTvp15rj4NVfRM7pKwNvTUnVXoWctA9VIGAmzX7E5QKSltF4bG7OENHN4FOOXr6X+T8795RTfQEAqeLSX21xkw2Om01YhzmZAxUvZ+CSTOdxJJn0APSX6kiivXtvq4Jp1zSNeL4LQ9krFVQJhWWSraIhIn2lWUjMWTRn0ojhdWxZkDYRx04JZDj9bfkiN73MawCzpRPXI5rfurhOWekkC7aa0+CF5e9IqjOMaf28isUvNWJgqX0F8BahdiNuRSAO4edRs\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8018","langCode":"en","question":"PeX6GYiz1V88ROd9Q3v17/NqSlsAvyI+0j+TwriPsHtWY739S9HqLDCs4u7dYlt7yitX/YTR/s9brQNSygJFeA\u003d\u003d","answers":["count on","get down","do away with","look down on"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"Rk4a3b9xZPPAfccJCSFS6OJbM/YdGKIY/Xmas6DjNPHgfKARELVXaT0OSTrPpwwRewvXEhiaTN1r5t72xD+l9G5HWOZKEeNfu1x1O6tzRLgX2M7kJA082RKlK3osw+TQws17OjHY5WXTqgHx0DoUHzL1l+RZYlLRjWSrJ6PLO26MTHCXsqk25bbNndNOvJhkD9NEsOHLUhdPTRTL4YQD4zyy0DjHDBkpBs7FPnfzo8mINT/EcTTnsv7cz/yrwA31Xf0jfCy7BPmSQDhM5E2rkbHKVcv/8Tm7SxsDjDIMPa0dE+eNfSfNMriywjko4CySu7TuUlyWGrGtDiiq+a5yJgEiO9pQE9TlwBGQUigIyIN7GUTfu5JfQutmnv5qetMNBFRBIz7BT1YEzKEetaaG9cIRSgoy8+kqwn44nPasijqq/mUVEzentvMDMnGXefkE"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8019","langCode":"en","question":"sx/nmCgyg5SwjCoyPhB4Zgl60z0ctlxKbo1oNNzU0QbXpjGZiMIKDFY/o/RzMIXjhG8yGSMvH/7wUDZiLf6R4Q\u003d\u003d","answers":["call on","call off","come up","fill in"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"ecntaWE1AGj3qZDT8uUyBmAP9f89U5QyG+if4sR9Ux0N/UeNcFogjZ2aST5owmgPAJioEvJrIdw8zRSUghmUhwfKChVibBsFVwLzaMaCXNRVEI28TCQUW+7RWAkM5cRRAaNN/s49SgO9sP2Rzdz0YTU+G97zF/utWViOhO9qCRiaD8FK9Legnx+N+wp0W36hHsbTJA4PK+hU3pKIQ+yiZ7RfGdVtYoC3X4C8uopVs5d2M3jEGbMAmwq+HwIT5SkH01Huop/kTD4PTeB3DHi49xqYbWU9ZUxDJLWZ5XM0ocrgrivcJ/OKpoaDjPS1ZSnKdNtqsLRdSfXlp+qe0iCrs70fMnStp+iKJ0gq18/USv9y+b7unkZFuSXPI+8AIuqP"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8020","langCode":"en","question":"+AoD28fZmPljy2tokaGqWxXpQOmKeRSbRPUJ6s0T08w\u003d","answers":["left out","let down","made up","burned down"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"do7uAkp/J2+0MlLPaNSp36n+EQ3mQYEjY3OrAdrkK7JU0mQwrtwjj2621IDY8sciU5SKLUflJkWODVIkNpJ9Rux70dRfk8kPHIY9HMOPkAgopycyp9hbmLGabhA3jpD8QG/UzKVzIfBMdSlMRhGyA18uebaBnPXKroWs4JWrgodESOzpl9Ub0D0oC/5iwBIRFtXXScfeEC0cP5obHge1ybZtPYmEzo/NfVptzMxFG+VUWuaYRQ6qcGBLDGLFO2Mye3Ogb2VzKaNymiCwqQ1fgDtv46+6alSeYLYxcinPtRXuz6ATsatrYNmsu8ksULZrC85t1A5Vct1+P6jl8grHjf0LRmBkpxpqEDMWN+BrETeIBumQvD6czkDWaMBemN3S6oM8q3lBvqvh7pe253JlWiWjpoOTIAVXDGht2SX3d0w\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8021","langCode":"en","question":"GGXKYP1s1EeKgNiS6qsvzGs+hJEDKdRwnOgYsYnSDOQ46o0mDyezQgLpI+P31UvHhNJRVLqeCs4v+xMUORD+L4OBUUh2JEYuu06tcR88n0c\u003d","answers":["pick up","put up","sent out","burst out"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"3B0zK2VCLSvetEdivB6AE5Y22XgVM8wnGLSp2pSyP8+5rTzo9BdQb4JFD70B3qC5fDPAqQzdRdqKzpr0v3l3Xnlsh2PSMPHzZxmrK63ejlKALgVfdaUbSdd24PsPAvT2IUH32yyMGbKpmhwtcZz0ZBTglFlCiQnIwQaVrzr5mMPVw4nEGV0RSY7IDUmjhwS+eyOVY2GO+04O7hNv6eEDmz81zuFlhhSZcHy2H+R7FKh2cSlunbQid/GaKbWY5KiXZTMvS3GkLbCEaZkNdU1qsoITvah18Az73NOfaN5sUCez2k1uWN5alDGsdgi66Zsfh9fKyhGZXzv4y4SlHEEyB1o/Je6OqAk9stD1l2KjpGVNP9VGOh0UZ8i7789fh8O8ZsxPk9mpBOTLuJw+SPhT5BZFO+6YrDgA9x45ieO7X4U\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8022","langCode":"en","question":"xP24iLjI8NORnDLgnvfYjxd7WdKYZD2TZttsbeUEW7e6duKOZmD1b2UgIK3rwJktViG5OCnNx9ZbYUg7ANhMSg\u003d\u003d","answers":["went over","broke into","broke out","called off"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"kU+os0AS6xH+l+3ruyD9R4fQhgzH5uWz992A+EoR1s15Mt6J5EokQp2AsFomPrCxCLngvR1WIb/8Lu3bnngLnGfMGAr+xH111vbpchSZT/tYwR5Ybuk/EnMedWjOKWH6fof5RavAXsnsEAUUerm7aYcscNj0VPBdLmQGaWRYrJ0vQEGAiMib70KwN6l5KfpV6gDe0HL/gFBrek/OHZt/v6fR+9hsKdEBrwElVDIR70WiEZDmgqIXCASSSX8fdWvdYuAizz3vSps+GIN6rAEXE8bPvCDrRDcsmb4kEiYgSbwdDXDSQyeVb12eUsBOKU/JeAb55mA3LLe1nHZcpqVufz4w8plE0DsuBrjfS2MEKZdLf3pw0d1LB14EUuIwdDBZxw4AQsg3VZB/nj8mqF4ataOeRjIuj0ze0D4lZaA+lfs\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8023","langCode":"en","question":"LRQS6dYdpfbmMcjmsxvhrun+9tqubbors2yXJ6YgO4C3tB/2X7vUL0tWaCbN+3iehG8yGSMvH/7wUDZiLf6R4Q\u003d\u003d","answers":["look up to","call on","take after","hold on"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"HOc0/0hTW6u/kNwW/BrxqeriAzEj7L9QCXfG8+FVVIk9a/13/7grzlQ6D6QFMT1uXQTdEECXh2+u3INSzrGusTB48r5MHGNH4eUungJoYzAjo7TP5HWJ51qE5blys2h9XL+qoVvhwgXI1wfGHk0C5qJhkI0DNwGapKPmA85aMR34xfZyBlSLeZ2/blRleUko3QmCWMB1LiLVUoJvTVMknN1HNwxJO5Nsjh42LR5zQ6evFZDEFNk+LPRsthE/TITjmYNyqqqFt/yLdhoqFXSU/HEVym9T/j+5smogzWouy5YhDY9r/6fF4EJPjRbIbpTvTzzRGYoHI38jAfnvVaseIQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8024","langCode":"en","question":"ytr/uBHWNQieAxZpzLaidgu3+kSPxSpIYiJSMynXQ55K3r4txlieYJYeoTh9Qnj459MDd2JpHjHLCxxLQj9lLKX0M4XzTS0YAU0Jqqw/ieE\u003d","answers":["run out of","turned on","cut off","went away"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"055z9NLN+Gt3hks+u2tamABddxrZhTPmXBUjgx4uycqszm2K4Z5NYf2Kq3UpxfTCEzrqLwewF8LQhN3aLfnPRkV/bJeC1JBL1CIcuqYyY41Zs7TOXo5nUZ+Wt2HOrOscSL9rGmtBKyAkjKT2Oew2zhfigEOM1fPVJ8kH8O/QaeAh6bWZJsUCUtjzsOB8l8h3cXn5EBD9yvYFIFWuussqfo2/uWWFqgnKszyQeSIs71L/u64igNqMKwqEb62J+hFwpseOpWnsH96yQK97o19dIW/KxunbPkkGoMTLr+z61Qy4HAzHK+EwE1UogRMKk1gqLyq7bO/mx69I46LcFgswoQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8025","langCode":"en","question":"/Uu9OnYy7w9OzB22epojowKKN0wZQwBEwryElu/s7dppwpa80eMqMpwmK1q48uVx","answers":["cut down on","catch up with","fed up with","take part in"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"rMXI8Sj9TjOh15hd8KEgsOfvZk2JaAK9oTraydHct2cd9I5Px/Fbwuk6zh1Z11yMGTgp5pOmwOJ25VGjqsd42NjjI10fkue9zxwQkLUf+y3LKmnRz/Rz0aSVJ/9FLGqlRNY0/gFVO1WHaCdzDBJB96wOb/7HtM76oUtqf+fncf+SjjF0fAeExQ5vI2IcJlZlK25xGYvx/csHGivlR/xpMU+wMCEisVLYiP/Z1CjLJgKxZslgLZbZdYnvGxnQZqys7FhagzFCzVC5BSAFrKQVtBzKGTsHf0mk2/4Exq9KnyxitRbOSeI8oJaZpYm6P3kyPptJsgP8wFH9d0B9REddEeEUlp3SyWS1N+bFVB6xdIrW4d6cxOyVon6MbQ90ijWXG348RwEm3I1oJ33cd466JbYWflJq6WgTDsg1rQUAciodTv9LJlER4A38vu4n/phRE00CHW9iOokr/XtNkNkxvVCojmubDXna4aaUwE4XNr3pgKK4tido/t7yr64SSYmeYbvpx9SL/9n4KWGAoztuYHZIhU8fYlKO2o7Y/RaDt/BXqZTlbz32gpwsOdEdpdNKt0rbUMMdE11M88+o5L2ChggDzbTi2pQt8KgyTbGhFB/BIqQi264VqttTCeYBDCwU"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8026","langCode":"en","question":"IBSsF3xKmdNWN4p2S2+VhGguWIWV1OsJx0C/y5W2OFhTFMkb0u97Ok9OlgcaUJuSo24kCzsz1FMeHxtzl1Zodw\u003d\u003d","answers":["dying out","calling off","dropping in","carrying out"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"GYaOdRW3k+Xsvl1ulQAoY9b7GuUMvhtg7JHI3pKox7IKPsS9EgTjZ6KWiUnWP9tzxs38lCST8m6UasaM5GvPWVRhcj2bLA1wDW8AkxDZEy0JeP/BtaVUwDwl9Y05eBhL1ACpxd5PDqWkHTy8iS6uWKUgMXJD3tlyE57Lmpw0xp3q2U6E4Cviq8PfFzYZewLMAw9gfjDkwJZXos4hbkUDrieNj+gZGhXShf9SA2t1YmJ0wA8QTIAoUOp3gMgcCXEx5cqI6Y9nAeI2QEO9DAH1glPKiF6dzAbp0HEHZue0viytyJ/y0K3cLCGbL1x8Eup6QWJ5NO1IosMKGgaZzj7B32ISpwSlp3Jdv7j5YKjYdHPNx255MIaG5l3VZClXCwkkhG8yGSMvH/7wUDZiLf6R4Q\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8027","langCode":"en","question":"3JC/lEFhtSuuf6Zg6TuyPkSDe6UGMtHYu/9B/YPJCbHb6DhgHEefHCkRUE8thF4Zu/GSiJodMHc8wTh16Y4mbg\u003d\u003d","answers":["get by","get over","get down","get up"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"Dv5lVsksiHzR3IE5khkbEzBbbViVg6rIcunlMPiKyQZLamb489DnUKHbp8AOwZtPX+uB4uN5I/P/qW4LIY/Dv0Ui/LfHVddv4wuF/6dbIVMdakmvlUN3LV6ZEVNrhKe3yhLi3d0H5w7TL83SRkrqsDBVl1dkMrGaLWUPXMA0LN3gYjyy01La9d6xC0dwW/yIsuLLyZ1PMwrN/u+kOunTYkq+7EFv5z25sGeqGOArn2h+3d0596bk/dhq4lLCi0cbgsQEUDr2R9ZfdS0K4v8DjU6fEEp96gSLZyYGA/w3+7eykvCVwo1gho+NwhMvZRMibDv7MixE05yQN66ZSrvxk6urhwJr4HxfcRt0YGJodIubudxCcEBHXetqTtEOEvgc"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8028","langCode":"en","question":"O+TQdmCGdUrZZ6TRf1htVDJaP4v+H3oQBtWs6m5R7rMiH2Mh3sXCSw4mYoHKXny2dp5ygNQSiOHskzBT6iHSmRUCDMJDB4T68lOynILUF6CRP2x5FJ2/p4kwQnKx2Zxe","answers":["find/out","cheer/up","get/down","calm/down"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"Ao48KYmuC143nuqMmBGSVgZt6UhlHUAbuv0ZPorp+ssHBuXQk8NJANoyuUa16DZC6Ybc0lkxCpdGeINsZFLq+c9yowFmYUAB054QLggcUCrcUu2k2+339eHfi+EyJy5ftt7wDW8MeqL51iMyBrOX0MOIxnJdyJlYPAfPSDAtZYW7G0YSKVvP5iDx0iKwtaTXXCULdArd4F/XgHAMxfa6CkPvSgST2i+9jgx6VPJSr0RVeJn1zuEL9+0v0zh7gGVxWfHIs4ZAkilrUprVmQU80eGWXmvwkYIFLqTMf7Lco61iEqcEpadyXb+4+WCo2HRzzcdueTCGhuZd1WQpVwsJJIRvMhkjLx/+8FA2Yi3+keE\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8029","langCode":"en","question":"2MV5QGX5HPC10hmxobWnpK2PTJDk/KZj0jQmeDXRI38UaTifaxAWl17VyITTizjs","answers":["looked on","died out","woken up","fixed up"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"xShTFHgepQx1lIW3eAtdFoe0hid25us6kgXLG2xpC94nP213BU3bEs31RUFbpTKJNCHI6pqBHqpJHWIcxWh3rDPXqomgiqgJujbjE/fPPqajnyq6ECEJCkdHRO5jdCsT6gFZ1iDQw4CvAxdlU97Oy94+1vQ9H9rwnHHWHeB2O0/Fle+5yxduNjpgMcAPZVFqaKVoN82ob+iTaeKM9N27VfhZGfmFpPwTlAQ++sqrgSwPzj86m9aqiUEFT0dAwa1eBUjHnX87P6BZar+NR0FWzqElvpmXWu4vO8vSphqVIeKwd0zzOiQcL4cFKQ2Lo0hRgENcMc6pzwqlEUAfaMFoqJNzAvGVLJN5Y9FzfIoaqyECi94C8A0iWHVQhugFJJgOgSc7IrrRfJnqqjvQWCJoykMZK0ZLmqh0PSuULh4GH9qSxX51ztT6DobCjt6ecrohIQ2Pa/+nxeBCT40WyG6U70880RmKByN/IwH571WrHiE\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8030","langCode":"en","question":"Ohcbz09rxYo3QfHoZc8apKZaaoIp5jI5WVsgtNxzJzZEO20RwOjeIQtzj7oi4V74KzP2K4qm7LslvC1xlgSMSw\u003d\u003d","answers":["went off","warmed up","accounted for","speeded up"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"2E4wIAeb0eqU66eapv+wwxOE5QjqCQvuPmxHZKVUdRPieEpaqzsxuCjT68dyyYMFVTwduDneOSUpLRso+Jd+pSt8gf9clzcBQQATogK5fMZ77GIh17sWqdEZ34ZwSocFQMFE7vn6XRt6oYyxOiFOhFyoZfBXvIPAcR7i4CW0oYH+aTz4xSWS4bgQU6LOKYyGMyYb2SFY8qtnJGsCAGu7P5HTZ7mwb1Ak7YuJ+7Mz6/WTrGRJ1CqPJZkhXUti2YBvUKif1GJZ2u08+FSiICFDN8rWVxu1UIYYrZ7Oyr9rc06U4guzUneqoy0nEed821DnxeId1UjllKlaqkgduh1262bMT5PZqQTky7icPkj4U+QWRTvumKw4APceOYnju1+F"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8031","langCode":"en","question":"MDP+5LrRr2GRztuQi8IkhMRZWVjOKAg3OkmQiIPhd3rJvnTydbXUSL8Lp7j6MqCm","answers":["come up with","back up","cut down","break in"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"0+QW2HVIAegtyeGiXaeTMC1eBpS8o6YY7ntFtVSt1LuuMvRt8UPtcI/5GCoCKevcjMA94TbE+heELzPPiQaURmufY4141renIs5AABEAznDlOS0XwmtuH5wjH5HYeOa0v+hSEMk/5D8Cu8PRNAMK8EAdA6CodWXbmrEbey1hpgdYqnkwUShKyoIVjGZ/5SbIbzAYPi5snGPGVLZqwwPbQzpwaZnXhgvbiTdirLWeGr19DVi8ircUJO9Xl93bdEjpuBuL/Pppp/rBzW2xZKEKy4cadrRiFLeoxFq9Kqjh+KU81rD4AR1RRer9tRwYBcuAdGgYEGg2Vr+ATJNO9lz8U7+jBIfpYGawXznR+O4HZ6rhdxIsXRH8aIDKRG5os8Vgnm33cnv7WgPMUAd5+1K+vWDK6ooUe27oWX61r6WGchdrv6rUDyyBknbPMVxdbtwPQfN8/CEcV0FeLrR2uk6ukw\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8032","langCode":"en","question":"koTE/Vioxn4G1iIanEX7ZZ/zOped8qxSapDIgRW+EWoy64NnH55MTI8aTd1KcvM7KRS7Gc/eeX0yPlLpHn0BcqltQFmrY04HCDEVkYSR1kc\u003d","answers":["bring up","look back on","hold on","fill in"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"KHQV46TKJv3oIeAZY6CZdOxcvJ/c34Cz1SdF5GT93oLQH2ApUWZ+1mXxpvANuvdWsXllQNHSWU7DPixKRwuxlVJKTwmKPp2uBkCOlCyccDHEgf4QPT5EssFH0EQCU2Acx78EDGYfEhDWDkYSMo/1EJgJt/Ln9xCGofyukJ8+q5mliOf/2acXuW2GEFQvZb/J3XTkHQ24MvFerXgyQ+3CSmT9b/rbwiFmLFbvDV+2vodYOqdywA0l7qjv+NXVTCPsOqUwPmUpt/u9qn/aUMzFBOjdFBPIUvtbc0f07yN4ofjFbxBUWZ2BQjohSbXfG44X21yqkSSdEHOpd9JWWPZMdF1q00H3ND8kAsSrhknWZpRpDS3oMjHYVXcuQhIQa5PTCAPNtOLalC3wqDJNsaEUH8EipCLbrhWq21MJ5gEMLBQ\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8033","langCode":"en","question":"QmcP1fK15Vna7ug1NBz0xB4C98XiwFdNXo9kQ2QlHSeC0aRS57Q7GOZSLm/zIcYu","answers":["got on","went out","called on","blew up"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"NK5sUwmieV6c3FvI1Yxs9mW+KAhkrjYKzXJZ4hWrfdRA/U9BEIxb2n+6gFrupUoaX2DCSRFZQb97S1CNqUFwc5m0IMsZlNZ86Gmknk/a2aF3azkjlbZLBoT/0d/7gKDZY74LF2MZueEqoSCrHrEFGuxayXdBsUeccslJBGrAc2nYkcwJZML1XpW9oc80xpovVwDqcMYETQUZyaL+ZpbLh5h0QbT3Hz58xWN1e/GkaeXmSclaM9obj6RGiqmYpHbCNyQQRspifbMsUdtFG7e4usTenacaVhOJVyFRZ8LNzn2KclKiO1XzgCi6NodtFe8lOnUdwbRczT+Lt/LAHhEY5d48Wh2fSaB+iZoalyn7LYZm4c9fdkGC90gGag3AZeBaIQ2Pa/+nxeBCT40WyG6U70880RmKByN/IwH571WrHiE\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8034","langCode":"en","question":"4aBpZIF1DsoRahqw1vZGQ7U6hab8aVhqXSdnXkEP0IRMLEPnubIA4hmUjgOxlW2KhG8yGSMvH/7wUDZiLf6R4Q\u003d\u003d","answers":["turn down","come about","break down","call up"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"6TXWSXrsQQmZhDuGQeQZtMcnHhcrZHwFrl5LgAz4hd+2p9FGJTIWEP0q5ajR2765uoNS9EswiIi6ZPwLAKwxp3g9pg2HxtvEslupcESXKv1IWVmo4D1MPq9gTXbMGZ/e46aT+tx8YnrfqkAUyO3nm9+L6oyLjNf6dTPUXNe+gzcfOA9IdB2i8S6Cw9NXpVTisXYwnaJ9v8YeS4LFwcPMTNzWZbLeF2d8l/yuwg4/tnAc7Yt5o2enH0jn5X9KAaLI/4DECDcb46yWoKhbLOiqg0nKFE7OO3I2J2wait6i83DgeJmT2Vmep76otCTr4fZYQ2Me63nL4DS6/6m4V6hKF2u/qtQPLIGSds8xXF1u3A9B83z8IRxXQV4utHa6Tq6T"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8035","langCode":"en","question":"YbYf79MvCGEcUrytZLPsfc1pbseSTC92gVAt8EqXHu69c2oirYoplhFHCTPm17UdLfapOsmVthd6BxALbebzvg\u003d\u003d","answers":["carried out","dropped by","fell down","thought over"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"lpy6MBEGhXQQ+ZydAy9HOxou00lmPlV629NLSHLVpXZqn7PAgFbptd93jBHe+3YBdBSzBOqed9b/eCpk0drFouXhLbiStDBpAxNwtGR+XHkVQ/EhFtJZraPCz5VVjFCf2z/ECxPDp0g7tAiJkrdZcaiCMizcGWAkNyKScLOS1E9vDyQScfKqfR3uKmzGABLcgI34b9nxCi49mSzHR1a3X3JfAnOo+GW9Hz0/Y7s/cnUHOolXR57YyhktUwSdnrO4QLIJDXwX0aW1zatGRmmxMbCy1FKtsawQtKv0JjqlheZAlV7wNH1ZR+37nTRTGslrbKNAZOVB/Rw6cZQMz2+ZFYgYjCnE9M7V/yItDa/eUZqZtCDLGZTWfOhppJ5P2tmh+5AoaNskbr5tdN7m3q+kFQf4rj2jKXP8pqkSvkfP7HAUTMVIi4b349A4/dtLz8olS396cNHdSwdeBFLiMHQwWccOAELIN1WQf54/JqheGrWjnkYyLo9M3tA+JWWgPpX7"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8036","langCode":"en","question":"dYTylbcsoXxCAeE9eLS2iVzu98ulz8ma97AkDUICSE49TeLT7WbN7mTaaDapeiW5EkIbYyreeeq8HPGz3MFaag\u003d\u003d","answers":["put up with","came up again","delighted in","caught up with"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"bebuHHziWLY8j5roGHUNflzW4tipGUtNw4MwYf39YSWmLJXNpnhWKiEMeIPervMOGbDx8l8zf4NoNewIohhajDobf9gvOuAX5NKHOi0ZTfiwkB5PWTc+LNDAbBkkZH7lTqWsxG697N7LVbGZ8oXNvoa9KsJzHAM/LjKOAbcLPvmwosvxAVvRNcl0EO9qkZJck7RTRHB8SuUXfSYM8y/xZVXmDkNOLo9AXNqaHgjnLJ5pLC3WmN6Ypwd8z6YeI/t9KLsNpA+lyEk0cvcleEqL/EL7fepf5Pfqswnvm992CN6zwgji2+4F02fibh23F7uvPN2O+kYYbqmnTnv8FkAQl0MYiuy3ERPGzyeAC5DP65kFYOOco4fwcD5HC/9bJLnu7s83/0SVFjB5X0t4KsRewV0OTkc5H1VC9rwSubqyQhbdLXBMEcrZtk9DTcLyHLG6dNtqsLRdSfXlp+qe0iCrs70fMnStp+iKJ0gq18/USv9y+b7unkZFuSXPI+8AIuqP"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8037","langCode":"en","question":"E2siED9q/opwOAEJ5qw19tjj+MnRqVJ4RwbkUVh+xhpfNqWNdMMnSscIhpaR2A7E","answers":["putting up","running out of","clearing up","looking forward to"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"T71ZqOnqlw8YHfhnjFAGeuue7UAR0bwPHuQcrj719dyI5zOyLs0c8f1TFN6E5w6D6YVwWpHoitizPoJpkO1WV3GhpVIufnhF5BzNU0rvv9G/P92jJbDiz8nlSn/nV0iRn+49cOXLxDWrjqPc/AQ4PZPFaZKDHfzyJJSXTIMD26bdCVdHW/6jUeazI2gm+pBvupVAFApHI0Pi4tTD0ZQ+mQ5jFELQkwjVfoO6g2zWYmjTiytSEs9ge4t9+FET1QKzXeTCLxWTJdhzoMKKLqubsVZeFXc/jYWDV2zStUofcb/N40cXGbkOY91V92PX3pCos7cUP+/rq17P176PWSYwy2JQuvSa8sYKWHMF53mr3wzcCqgqRkmQen/A3akuoF2utVUODdij2ujqueBKZTpfGQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8038","langCode":"en","question":"rWYnU7XRfHiOygU4UTfAvp8J0AJH5f7q7pwfEoJ8yJxFd7SeZZKNKm9+um3CNOna0xybrAsCyisLp+7zrSJavw7ilQ/yRMD/8ZCVLkoOvrmEbzIZIy8f/vBQNmIt/pHh","answers":["left out","given back","come apart","covered up"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"zLkxx7a2bBqWa/wG62U+yn9YzxP6EOyiXWX147wYnThpSu/FIeRZXDonVjqL1sn649sNLEjsjP22A7VKHRet3+UGyMxg/eKfLLgSd+KzrVCT5i6zfq0bcLXFI2F84YyCgT79wHIYImUNHYu/j7TS/mEUMqLvHwpkl7KBvgyyBIMX4kx4TWB86mkL7YDkF//Tv4cakD6kJa55IWMASuGVe4B5Jdsb52/QEpxp5EawbQDPoI/G7/YdkJzwIzPCFFgfbCu58b0ZQ/Wk5YFMfL2s6JIEs+6Wkr4LqqkzPhCBtJWYi+i7pnDTNjSVIuBuMiIyJFIuK6g3SQKNsh1TXFAERw\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8039","langCode":"en","question":"Nc6C+eKmA+EG1ro0vmfV9/buH55KvT3NZxcRXQWsQoQ\u003d","answers":["come up with","dream up","throw away","face off"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"rrGdER8TuJVl9Wnbf2F7+r0UV+hRw1rGuiCO6mldGxzapKOJNiy6iJ14ekU51VGnM7sRWvXHy/c8jpg3dmQdqB5Hlx9elEAU5v5Y4bd9NdceqH6oV9X/QAp4inQlOXlm82WNCHKtlZPvsBZqIBNxr81OKnX0uJFbGSgVmZ405URLzXjMY3f5WUVj2HDDF9m2ZwPoxoZjCFCKsY0gUa8f8MYngyKkq+JCdo4fqi57o88q8nUB0Iy1RgCqyka5TsB+3AnGhlI1auNd6zY2PsOXyssbDe05VtH8dKn27X/dk9o1dKCnljV4rkOBRXENCHgCwlYKcSF51kqwug5tcIYBvbgcDMcr4TATVSiBEwqTWCovKrts7+bHr0jjotwWCzCh"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8040","langCode":"en","question":"KNwnopUHab8J1XKpc4owYB2NSG2WYvWtEeCTjrdp/bQYejVB/4Lzd5w7jzHzZwPjCs0zOI2zb8L13Hf754T7ZA\u003d\u003d","answers":["help out","work out","look up to","join in"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"0QJWRjoVDX/cvm11ZapNVzt2m30Gz5Tm43NjLmk8FVf205cf+eM3F/4U1SkFgUntCZvEt4Th2JxxTrugaPMZ9GhbuWpbcjfU2bSPJK/JOlb0JvO79B7dGQun6Dz19TXWUfLVBuFAorhNAaYUk4/R041AYnSqGZFVquMB1HmGO9ZsihoTkvtmBh0VCu6XNco6Ez4NxVnpJdNvIDbRX2gI2NI2BGKSKJPpgYTPdeBc46sCw5SWibifiHZLvYXAZi7jJx4scmbehAn9gEnde1ZkBNACrGoE2Kh1mMF8WQfxvA4d69P81xdV9L6E1ZPZYJTKihsZExdTG0wdlaBZ9TUusDgx0o8bN/KzW62X8bEjUXzFqd8TqhHov7z8Fs8WdhgFxqTQZgRU2W90D4DA/owbemu/qtQPLIGSds8xXF1u3A9B83z8IRxXQV4utHa6Tq6T"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8041","langCode":"en","question":"GUhNr9Y0D2FLFbviX2GwX9itvMPsFyDPGRqv9iwHOw9Yu9nqLZDffuJkuSxZ5e1SVIC+wjrbN5po07yMmxwOEQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["operate on","show up","own up","note down"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"FN+0XazjL81iWbG6/W2VexFPFCo0cI9eWtrfr24mUesUHwFGU3w8nGFuBtxLESdkvaFKPd8HoH3DdWi3r/ZF5n+xYhErZzQAD/n5aBrcM1YWinJTLhB4wiKcpMJ1uxgM22VWf1Zn8jL08TtKdutG3MFYjyCGFVKl4SirHbYJRinM86DrGW9g1yGBf3YDpipfbMvxKKkM6elTeKc0DOmVdsqwI+PQiAX4cOnqQHjcd+3L5mHf12SSw7IV/WRC8mRNUT1yOa37q4TlnpJAu2mtPgheXvSKozjGn9vIrFLzViYKl9BfAWoXYjbkUgDuHnUb"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8042","langCode":"en","question":"Wg+Idl/R+8RoE42H6hUkEeoTHjMjuY5vqo36uEAHVSOdFQZ7qHntKEE90JVn88WhXbZTvmUpB+dZuPlbIo+2SFSAvsI62zeaaNO8jJscDhE\u003d","answers":["lay/into","kick/out","keep/in with","talk/over"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"oi9oehsB/QYGbxP1qZZS0yI3WYz/+vsk8Psmc6TXk+5qwuwI7aSJn0zB2utYuhwGZk0Xry0x6mYU7/nkbW/pgFsZRK+1Lm/vqCS8ACkc39gn7SpyVrqFmWghFb8KFsvVIIW8mwYy9iCcpxvwqcJfG7OULn0tZwFF0YlWSZdyR9HohkbqEYs1P8/5ri11VLONlpOQdHtImwT/87Q9v2ZMKk11RaYaX4jeTkoq1zsDbWNlpriP/KzOTsJKjEV9X5TjY8hCKlUdFHbUYUwEmQTI7C+XOzU14FM0iT0AqZPtDXUNgEU0yuYan82vif472vnmYf4GFk0ADKorhc3SifBiLifLugr/jG93vgSq1RBev8lNLBXeUHi40ouqNaiCcqEWV/MbefQCtSB+eScEXApjKeLImGWwsoLruGKS1/MwIMU\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8043","langCode":"en","question":"SNFwdUIy08Y6sY/4v8ncI7h3PaCuLMiZ2pyywu+QGBF7V9U3UOCqqHbasGT2HRR9","answers":["look up to","look into","think over","make up for"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"j0VLGJ19wyLyW/J90qjgyfv2CClEfDZzbUdcARYx9swi/12WjhxZ37FssDMS2lHzMY2p4kI94yhVE0RRCguXprGAJnRVK3pH051s/OlW2WDJFp7crvsVc1FwHxgLzmGIk6UvBdXKqzgYxRQsvatZxgnC4zZicVgIUW+4ik9Wo6SET9z4Q7bChWduMptbIQhyA0xXu7OE1NQEW896mwqnZmXqtJBCLUO0CD4pEnF4RXm20WJGAn70RDWB1YmlwA9v1iB5/Clxf7e0ByLXgSkM75/A9z57WKKyyzuYPsA+hj/G3bDTOwVsLwfO0KklyyGYJ40e/bGsRKQEYux6j4bJbhEwsp7vvf+6TtTfTvgO8wnpty7cMkR71Z2bZMM+VZubG/wUiK406UtUthmbC9jigH6X82ZmSj22CoapT2TMzWhFsJuF2miFx4WAuUix0CUmwhFKCjLz6SrCfjic9qyKOqr+ZRUTN6e28wMycZd5+QQ\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8044","langCode":"en","question":"hRevVMShvTr6tR17wC3XT8cb1asIpIdIwJuCqH0/TBy0KfOT6xJ0GJRAVrYl9v+Y27Krz1kXdz22TqdA8S3BQlSAvsI62zeaaNO8jJscDhE\u003d","answers":["nodded off","queered up","run across","put up to"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"pS4jTE3Qonc6nzTa0/yN6yH0PMtWIEpTPmI5lAzIFQHr4IYdIgAHrEs5Ck7u036qPcJYhtLNI+mc7Ij3MOhR7rDJ0Sz4WNVk6jEwulqPp9FQNb3edXRjhnoUOPvwrZMzc8fBo2TD13c9sc0Jo/T8H4Fhz98r0I+xMQvWwt4NUoKUOFHpVFh6gttLkESMZ33bxBvjkEOiolMxbakdSj80JG9yU8d70ylFQngcbsW6+uWWcGGU/iU+R+yngfqOeBKOQkzy7X3lFi0gfMjsm1AsePLhbeBgycKcTXJI2kKrjo71kfJEUu1ddW4bg5NfwS99cJHuWGUX4EGi9VcjVEM1+eqDPKt5Qb6r4e6XtudyZVolo6aDkyAFVwxobdkl93dM"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8045","langCode":"en","question":"rU+PCXkctDqxpBxB/1dYxaMobFhJX/VAZDsDgNut/VeVIu/SNy4FHFkzfuJmIQHLVnYeNAmu3tiNrTL98O3EIw\u003d\u003d","answers":["run after","read on","keep on","ride on"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"qxfbdJYMRmAnWTzLeaYuMPaCAs5xh1y2ucy/NT20vfqxnL0RKubeXI1MeHeWOzqNm5MSELK7gGoJ8aNVCMoo3+Opm1Eh7SK/S9ZcYFf8cxjE/3yD0Rv10+tKDpOQZIUueljqY3l7B0mpaNCMsh7WeabLqmGnrmEJZjNBUazJlPKYNdZhxdmtfiLz0SRYyY9LwLFBA51+TmnfGvrFSVLvZE3jC69m6HkQ2T1nM/H5XNLSnNoBeICEyJfwmAnzHgCO5jsvk9VxqC50byzk1pUxytzYhwaSYLlgneppJGhmbZpTr7fkb6VRDizz7kghMV6or+iJenuC5+kGoFm2ewRXnnA+LNBRQcPFGNUntwltyDJPa/QF9zH6Lg47Hw3HZigRUqFyOW59/68ntpP6wXub44QQ2rOxoKUh9LPlk6tezfcrbnEZi/H9ywcaK+VH/GkxRFVJtgaq1uR9f5nv2JKteXZMMxvwAOUFvWr2D5gKbHmrq4cCa+B8X3EbdGBiaHSLm7ncQnBAR13rak7RDhL4HA\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8046","langCode":"en","question":"G6XG7ombU2TN4xTl62JO9NDraSzL/Htuk83XcCJz+hglQCJdW5jdORvxoELSz3uw","answers":["get in on","get behind","fall behind","wash up"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"mIEyfJQDL9KgoBiT1k/lr+GRffcakiho9/GWFoqYVgnhNS8nn4AgszSxMKYDfsYW5/mI9LhzeE8azbEGmLGLEvQhPzv8SxxheqZy0IXmb8N2IOBNVX2pZ1EU4R1Wqq1O3v89iypzpvZByaZFcj0ZdwO1a4J4eLBxvvatGI0bjE87s1CtKca4yqa0Jmm0CEtL+8MPimczrFq1jvd7s2XxboVS+A1n5lMrhqy0L86jT0kj1YOJv5z+bfZRnqWmR+G0j6/7EJlgTxdulxnLs3jq+MvRbJKIT2q7JzBdAXnvaccB+6Y1CKYV6G1A48l6s41h1kWvBpzktDosvPYHJ4XtggxpK0nsbmjdfDGBXt1oQcTXZ3t0bmqB+Zg/3D6SxPDuZaEml8MV3y1g4RLx2y6nRh/nmoXT13YoIiQ8erTbFPBiULr0mvLGClhzBed5q98M3AqoKkZJkHp/wN2pLqBdrrVVDg3Yo9ro6rngSmU6Xxk\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8047","langCode":"en","question":"ro/7DANSc8JCjarCoUcJRwl1iTDgPYV1KAB/H8i0Eb3/N4eRq6CcHrAClj/Yy26M","answers":["run out of","set aside","bear out","set upon"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"hIDv2dFHQ/Fq66EVvjwDqbTC4+S4oEoOKhatGLyHPArTnnP00s34a3eGSz67a1qYAF13GtmFM+ZcFSODHi7JyqzObYrhnk1h/YqrdSnF9MITOuovB7AXwtCE3dot+c9GRX9sl4LUkEvUIhy6pjJjjRFwzrtWNmlHh2adEbWa5RpS8GGbZEBH0N3vxPn3F0BBE3BC4Akc0vye63ye6S2BZl2dOZDujFGUuSZ57CkTZ5heAgKVL9II/AkstbTpFWEP2fOe9TzQCeK3rYB+IKYTdHTbarC0XUn15afqntIgq7O9HzJ0rafoiidIKtfP1Er/cvm+7p5GRbklzyPvACLqjw\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8048","langCode":"en","question":"0F96hkMEo9wVktoh/V4L/A23q9pD6Twe5bEz1G+/juRVcghLqppIVrH9VmPQXZmvYYfdJIgdQQZD54eU1Z+D9Q\u003d\u003d","answers":["slept in","settle on","speeded up","saw through"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"enTeNdNNYC+XqFFT6L3plV2Vq0HcjGitnlj/0BkeP5cGNwPbjWyBc+Ksb3Y6kv5f6lm+A8PbX9BNZKF906labQVQqzxV9dNVwCHcwbn8wiOF/EF0sQ5SQnElKoCBbrz95si/OGwDQ0NjM58I788JvAJ9v9Qqpxz1wcPb86H/e/Nzzk69P9X7xorgZKigadidf/nTAQE3V6fOTTEvt8PNxBvkVQw7D3IWOw5BZunVJE3eRm8Z/o58daONazXbgB8MA2Y2WwDvmXPXWNa40gAnvyLpOCBPvWczil1KmHubPtwvOr5YNfoZXXtqSURNVYBFIVGO+rTXFXx1oa7dwRFOqi1leazABKybY+3PeSVuWsyrq4cCa+B8X3EbdGBiaHSLm7ncQnBAR13rak7RDhL4HA\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8049","langCode":"en","question":"hPHneGwg+N0414Yr1XUT97/GTn3joSbMht+LbQ5GjZ2wKnmATTEB5YXhdBsiUUxy","answers":["gears up for","stands for","pairs up with","gives up"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"QPoGSQvt2xjlJ/tRflDW9P7MdVhsZfDRPK6z96kz6mH+a3YxIBGBowXZGRf0vMKSOb0twPr29MfV5339/rzywwNlvl9KCMNAgl6j1e9u7TnER7ozkd+EJKbzbF1H1pA5q0yassLiIAUnrlsgTZKKzOKdgAMxPSXZ7MOOImzhr+2jOTha9BQSShJB6mQHLv8FO4z2Z1IHurEielWMGoygRQBKHncOZAwF9xF8ZoaU5yGCGGdLcJq46qK+lFhbW2bzABVBvx2bAbJOyHdNg6OtX74NJNHdMjdMWgnt0OdCaygobNliOaKTzcWOlxzbz9UjfFZMN9qB5kvh4T30DJcs4MIRSgoy8+kqwn44nPasijqq/mUVEzentvMDMnGXefkE"}]